Jehan Kobe Chang

kokobe.github.io | linkedin.com/in/jehan-chang-657896156 Palo Alto, CA | 650.946.7293 | jkobechang@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced full-stack developer with an emphasis on mobile applications. My technical background ranges from machine learning to Android development to virtual reality experiences, and I'm able to apply my diverse skill-set to various challenging projects. I am constantly developing new skills as a solo-programmer, project-lead, and a team member – all of which are roles that I function effectively in.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, IRVINE

BS IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Sept 2018 - June 2022 Campuswide Honors Collegium Dean's Honor's List Senior Standing VR UCI Programming Officer Cum. GPA: 3.92 / 4.0 Major GPA: 3.94 / 4.0

SKILLS

Java • Javascript • C++ • Python •
Kotlin • HTML/CSS • C# • Android •
Node.js • Sketch • Unity • AWS • GCP •
Socket.IO • Machine Learning • NumPy
• Jupyter • REST • Docker • Firebase •
Virtual Reality • Linux • Blender

COURSEWORK

Data Structure and Implementation Analysis

Design and Analysis of Algorithms Machine Learning and Data Mining Computational Linear Algebra Applications of Probability in CS Principles in System Design Operating Systems

LINKS

Github:// Kokobe LinkedIn:// jehan-chang-657896156 Website:// kokobe.github.io

EXPERIENCE

STAR LABS (SAMSUNG) | SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

June 2020 - Sept 2020 | Campbell, CA

- Engineered a fully functional mobile app and its internal pipeline.
- Worked in an Agile development process with biweekly sprints.

(Kotlin, Java, Node.js, HTML/CSS, Android, GCP, AWS, UI/UX, Github)

ESSENTIAL | MOBILE APPLICATIONS INTERN

July 2019 - Sept 2019 | Palo Alto, CA

- Designed and implemented core features of the company-wide Voice-Mode project through building a **Walkie Talkie** Android application.
- Launched full-stack systems with Android/Unity front-end, AWS backend, and Firebase database/persistence.
- Developed three scalable projects in the span of three months.

(Android Studio, Tensorflow, Node.js, Python, AWS, Socket.IO, Firebase, Github)

AMPLIFY.AI | SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

June 2017 - Aug 2017 AND June 2018 - Aug 2018 | Palo Alto, CA

- Advanced Amplify's Natural Language Processing (NLP) system to automate the process of ingesting training data for Amplify's AI systems, from customer's websites, RSS feeds, FAQs and call center scripts.
- Integrated **REST and AWS** to make their chatbots capable of providing daily news and performance updates.
- Completely automated the process of connecting UI design of a chatbot to the Amplify AI system.
- Increased workflow efficiency for designers. With one click, their **Sketch** designs transform into ready-to-use Amplify.ai Facebook Chatbots.

(Javascript, HTML and CSS, Cocoascript, Webscraping, Sketch, AWS, REST, JSON)

SELECTED PROJECTS

GUITAR VR | kokobe.github.io/guitar | July 2020 - Present Utilized the Oculus Quest's hand tracking to create a Unity VR app that enables users to play the guitar without any prior skills. Dynamically produces any note from one sample note and can play thousands of songs.

PETR CHAT | School Project | April 2020

Engineered a multithreaded server with a protocol that allows clients to concurrently chat with each other and read server information. Developed it with **sockets** and **network connections** in C++ and a Linux environment.

ML AND PREDICTING RAINFALL | School Project | March 2020 Led a team of three overseeing the design and implementation of an ensemble of machine learning models (decision tree forest, feed-forward neural networks, etc.)

machine learning models (decision tree forest, feed-forward neural networks, etc that predict rainfall across the Earth. Maximized optimizations through dropout regularization, bagging and boosting, etc.

GLORIOUS NOON | Published on Steam | November 2017

Developed and published a virtual reality game using Unity. It is **cross-platform (HTC Vive, Oculus Touch) with over 20K downloads.** Designed all 3D models, used physics-based interactions to enhance VR realism, and integrated UI to add structure. Oversaw the publication, advertising, and developer-community outreach/feedback on Steam.